Guide to the United Federation of Teachers Photographs PHOTOS 019
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: New York Teacher Photograph Files, 1951-1987.
  - Subseries I:I: Individuals.
    - Ferraro, Nicholas (Queens District Attorney) meets with UFT officials, undated (Item 3179)
    - Ferrerio, Anthony J., Dr., undated (Item 1227)
    - Fesko, George, undated (Item 850)
    - Fesko, George, AFT Convention, undated (Item 1078)
    - Festal, Glenn with Tom Hobart, Feb 1974 (Item 2892)
    - Fettes, Dorothy, undated (Item 5045)
    - Fewkes, John M., undated (Item 22)
    - Fichter, Margallen, Tuition Tax Credits, Mar 23, 1981 (Item 5389)
    - Fidell, Florence, May 1981 (Item 2134)
    - Fidell, Florence, with Shelvy Young, discussing the union's [UFT?] structure and seniority with paraprofessionals, Jun 27, 1976 (Item 4497)
    - Field, Fred at ED 9 and 10, dialog with Congressional Representative, May 1976 (Item 4257)
    - Field, Fred G., undated (Item 3212)
    - Fierstein, Alan, Apr 1973 (Item 2399)
    - Filardo, Ann, Apr 1975 (Item 3683)
    - Filarelo, Anne, Mar 1977 (Item 2894)
    - Finch, Robert, undated (Item 943)
    - Fineman, Bill, Oct 1973 (Item 2637)
    - Finger, Justin, 1972 (Item 1783)
    - Fink, Stanley with Dan Sanders, 1979 (Item 3241)
    - Fink, Stanley with Ray Skuse and Dan Sanders, 1980 (Item 3241)
    - Fink, Stanley with Sanders, Jan 1982 (Item 3241)
    - Finkel, Ernest, undated (Item 4595)
    - Finnerty, John, Mar 1981 (Item 2595)
    - Fischer, Janet, Aug 1975 (Item 3837)
    - Fischer, John H., undated (Item 274)
    - Fish, Hamilton Jr., undated (Item 2113)
    - Fisher, Loren, undated (Item 606)
    - Fisher, Sally, Apr 1973 (Item 2428)
    - Fitzgerald, Ethel, Sep 1974 (Item 3330)
    - Fitzgerald, Maria, undated (Item 5363)
    - FitzGerald, Ron leading Chapter Chairman's Course, undated (Item 169)
    - Fitzgerald, Ron teaching Chapter Chairmen's course, undated (Item 156)
    - Fitzgerald, Rose receives award for her contributions to the mentally retarded, May 1976 (Item 4409)
    - Fitzsimmons, Bob, undated (Item 5674)
    - Flanagan, John J. (Assemblyman), undated (Item 793)
    - Flast, Florence, Public Education and Religious Liberty (PEARL), undated (Item 146)
    - Flaum, Paul, undated (Item 867)
    - Flavell, Thomas, undated (Item 237)
    - Fleischman, Earnest, undated (Item 54)
    - Fleming, Robert H., undated (Item 553)
    - Flom, Claire, NY Alliance, honored at 1985 RA (Item 5665)
    - Flug, Artie, undated (Item 692)
    - Flynn, Jean T., undated (Item 5176)
    - Flynn, John E., Sep 1974 (Item 3197)
    - Flynn, Pat, undated (Item 3907)
    - Fochesto, Anne (President Federation of Nurses/UFT), May 1980 (Item 5420)
    - Fochesto, Anne (President Federation of Nurses/UFT) testifying before legislature, Oct 1981 (Item 5420)
    - Foley, Michael with Ray Skuse and Manny Kafka, Jan 1975 (Item 4788)
    - Foley, Neil, undated (Item 5772)
    - Foner, Henry, undated (Item 240)
    - Fonti, Vincent, Apr 1973 (Item 2401)
    - Ford, David, Nov 1971 (Item 1787)
    - Ford, George, Reverend, undated (Item 999)
    - Ford, Gerald is presented with pane of new stamps commemorating collective bargaining, May 1975 (Item 3665)
    - Ford, Gerald with James Harris, Jun 1975 (Item 3620)
    - Ford, Gerald with Velma Hill, Jun 1975 (Item 3704)
    - Ford, Gerald, President, addresses Congress, "State of the Union", 1975 (Item 3520)
    - Fortney, Robert, May 1974 (Item 3096)
    - Foster, Doris, undated (Item 949)
    - Frabk, Sylvia, Apr 1, 1973 (Item 2412)
    - Franco, Cecillia, Nov 1, 1973 (Item 2766)
    - Franco, John M., Oct 1, 1973 (Item 2718)
    - Frank, Joel, undated (Item 3512)
    - Frankel, Joseph, Rabbi, undated (Item 2386)
    - Franklin, John Hope, undated (Item 775)
    - Franklin, Norman, Mar 1974 (Item 2934)
    - Franks, Samuel, Feb 1974 (Item 2854)
    - Franse, Stephen, Dr., newly appointed Bronx member of the Central Board of Education, Dec 1981 (Item 5505)
    - Frantz, Ron, NYSUT Board, undated (Item 5101)
    - Fraser, Douglas A., AFL-CIO Executive Council, undated (Item 3671)
    - Frayne, Sharon, May 1976 (Item 4281)
    - Frayser, Lou, undated (Item 666)
    - Freda, Lou (Assemblyman, 49AD Brooklyn), undated (Item 5501)
    - Freeman, Frankie M., undated (Item 1479)
    - Freeman, Orville L., undated (Item 588)
    - Freeman, Virginia, Clarkstown Teachers Association, Dec 1975 (Item 4334)
    - Freudenberger, Herbert, Teacher Burn-Out, undated (Item 5519)
    - Frey, Thomas R., undated (Item 3213)
    - Friedenberg, Edgar Z., undated (Item 851)
    - Friedman, Charlotte (District 30 Election Candidate), Apr 1973 (Item 815)
    - Friedman, Eve, profile shot, Washington Irving HS, Feb 1982 (Item 1533)
    - Friedman, Irving, undated (Item 1025)
    - Friedman, Irving, Higher Education, undated (Item 1025)
    - Friedman, Paula, undated (Item 4567)
    - Fuccillo, George, undated (Item 358)
    - Fuchs, Danny, Mar 1974 (Item 2935)
    - Fuchs, Robert, CSB District 11, Apr 1973 (Item 2475)
    - Fugle, Marcella, undated (Item 3858)
    - Fugle, Marcella, undated (Item 3875)
    - Fuller, Paul, Dec 1973 (Item 2847)
    - Fuller, Paul, Harrison Association of Teachers receives check from NYSUT President Tom Hobart, Oct 1973 (Item 2708)
    - Gadson, Jeanette, Sep 1974 (Item 3276)
    - Gaeta, Anthony, Oct 1973 (Item 2344)
    - Gaeta, Nancy, undated (Item 5120)
    - Gaither, Louise, Jun 1974 (Item 3101)
    - Gaitner, Kenneth, Mar 1973 (Item 2313)
    - Galamison, Milton A., Reverend, undated (Item 656)
    - Gallagher, James, Nov 15, 1971 (Item 1725)
    - Gallagher, Jim at ED 14 Meeting, Oct 1972 (Item 2154)
    - Gallagher, John T. (Assemblyman), undated (Item 93)
    - Gallo, Don, Clarkstown TA, May 1976 (Item 4297)
    - Gallup, George Jr., undated (Item 4220)
    - Galvin, Barbara (District 24 Election Candidate), Apr 1973 (Item 2444)
    - Gambino, Richard discusses guidance needs of Italian American students, Jun 1975 (Item 3560)
    - Garcia, Nancy D., undated (Item 939)
    - Gardner, Arnold (Attorney), undated (Item 4504)
    - Gardner, John, undated (Item 303)
    - Garelick, Samford, undated (Item 2009)
    - Garrison, Lloyd K., undated (Item 273)
    - Gart, Rrita, Nov 1973 (Item 2785)
    - Gartner, Kenneth, undated (Item 990)
    - Gaspari, Amanda, undated (Item 253)
    - Gavil, Andrew, Jan 1976 (Item 3984)
    - Gavin, Andrew, undated (Item 4031)
    - Gazzara, Anthony V., undated (Item 3245)
    - Geary, Yvette (District 4) [x], undated (Item 5302)
    - Gelernter, Sanford, undated (Item 189)
    - Gelfand, Bertrand, undated (Item 994)
    - Gerena-Valentin, Gilberto, undated (Item 443)
    - Gershbein, Stanley, Apr 1973 (Item 2423)
    - Gershenson, Ira, Nov 1975 (Item 3894)
    - Gershman, Laurie, undated (Item 1602)
    - Gherstein, Cheryl, undated (Item 5362)
    - Gherstein, Marlene, undated (Item 1309)
    - Gherstein, Marlene, School Secretary, PS 94 Bronx, Feb 1971 (Item 1309)
    - Giacobbe, Joseph, 1974 (Item 3398)
    - Giardino, Alfred A., undated (Item 294)
    - Gierke, David C., undated (Item 5124)
    - Gietz, Raymond, undated (Item 4580)
    - Gifford, Bernard, Nov 1973 (Item 2795)
    - Gifford, Bernard, Dr., Jan 1975 (Item 3439)
    - Gifford, Bernard, Dr., undated (Item 3724)
    - Gifford, Kenneth, Oct 1974 (Item 3568)
    - Gifford, Kim, undated (Item 4627)
    - Gilbert, Jack (Hon.), undated (Item 496)
    - Gill, John H., Reverend, undated (Item 1721)
    - Gillia, Jerry, JHS 22 Manhattan, undated (Item 5622)
    - Ginott, Alice, Dr., Apr 1975 (Item 3696)
    - Ginsberg, David (Executive Director), undated (Item 501)
    - Giofsky, Irving, portait, Oct 1981 (Item 5483)
    - Girolamo, Joseph (President of the Miller Place, LI), Mar 1974 (Item 3139)
    - Gladstone, Irving, undated (Item 871)
    - Glasser, Diane, undated (Item 1711)
    - Glassman, Jack (Chapter Leader), PS 42 Manhattan, undated (Item 5614)
    - Glazer, Joe, undated (Item 4827)
    - Glenn, Don, [NYSUT Local?] Cazenovia TA, undated (Item 4970)
    - Gless, Susan, undated (Item 5746)
    - Glossner, David, undated (Item 2599)
    - Glosto, John, Nassau adjunct drive top 200 mark, undated (Item 2020)
    - Gobeo, Anthony, undated (Item 3761)
    - Gobeo, Tony, Sep 1975 (Item 3917)
    - Goffredi, Sue, undated (Item 4596)
    - Gold, August, undated (Item 700)
    - Gold, Emanuel R., undated (Item 2013)
    - Gold, Eugene, undated (Item 2242)
    - Goldbaum, Maurice, undated (Item 880)
    - Goldberg, Arthur J., undated (Item 268)
    - Goldberg, Bernard, Dec 1979 (Item 41)
    - Goldberg, Bernard with Reuben Mitchell, 1978 (Item 41)
    - Goldberg, Bernard, sworn in as member of the Teachers Retirement System, Nov 11, 1973 (Item 41)
    - Goldberg, Debra Sue, photo of little girl taken during CC meeting, Dec 6, 1967 (Item 338)
    - Goldberg, Jill, Jun 1975 (Item 3672)
    - Goldberg, Seymour, undated (Item 1978)
    - Golden, Howard, Best in Brooklyn, May 1980 (Item 2008)
    - Goldfarb, Robert, undated (Item 2487)
    - Goldfine, Ira, undated (Item 4742)
    - Goldfinger, Nat, undated (Item 1593)
    - Goldfinger, Nat, undated (Item 3206)
    - Goldin, Harrison J. with Dan Sanders, undated (Item 376)
    - Goldin, Harrison J., Political Action, undated (Item 376)
    - Goldin, Harrison J., with Al Shanker at City Hall, Sep 1981 (Item 376)
    - Goldman, David, undated (Item 2506)
    - Goldman, Jerrold, undated (Item 5083)
    - Goldman, Kathi, May 1973 (Item 2547)
    - Goldman, Louis, undated (Item 703)
    - Goldstein, Harriet, 10/17-18/1970, Oct 17, 1970 (Item 1420)
    - Good, Raymond, Dec 1973 (Item 2839)
    - Goodell, Charles, undated (Item 1253)
    - Goodemote, John, Griffith Springville Institute, Jun 1976 (Item 4350)
    - Goodman, Jerome, May 1974 (Item 3041)
    - Goodman, Laura, undated (Item 4849)
    - Goodman, Mark, undated (Item 3827)
    - Goodman, Paul, undated (Item 441)
    - Goodman, Roy. M., [New York State] Senator, Jan 1974 (Item 2814)
    - Gootnick, Lou leading Chapter Chairman's Course, undated (Item 169)
    - Gordon, Bertha (Morris HS Principal), May 14, 1971 (Item 1530)
    - Gordon, Edmund, undated (Item 840)
    - Gordon, Robert M., Lay Faculty Association, Jul 1973 (Item 2212)
    - Gordon, Robert M., NYSUT Board, Jun 1980 (Item 2212)
    - Gordon, Robert M., NYSUT Board, 3/23-24/1979, Mar 23, 1979 (Item 2212)
    - Gordon, Robert with Harold Isenberg, William Cea, Ficcio, Kaufman, 1979 (Item 3557)
    - Gordon, Sol, undated (Item 242)
    - Gotbaum, Victor with Feldman, Swain '78, Shanker, Bill Scott, undated (Item 239)
    - Gottlieb, Edward P., undated (Item 207)
    - Gottlieb, Herbert H., undated (Item 1290)
    - Goudis, Peter, wins NEA Human Rights Award, undated (Item 2156)
    - Grad, Arthur, Dr., undated (Item 1680)
    - Graham, Al (First Vice President), Mamaroneck Teachers Association, May 1976 (Item 4264)
    - Granger, Robert (SPA President), Apr 1973 (Item 2340)
    - Graves, Carole, undated (Item 959)
    - Gray, Charles L., Reverend, Apr 1973 (Item 2432)
    - Grayzel, Estherann F., Teacher Burn-Out, undated (Item 5519)
    - Greco, Stephen R., Aug 1975 (Item 3874)
    - Green, Ernest, undated (Item 347)
    - Green, Ernest G., Mar 1975 (Item 3635)
    - Green, Ernie, undated (Item 437)
    - Green, Myron, undated (Item 4358)
    - Green, Ruth, undated (Item 4904)
    - Green, S. William (Assemblyman), undated (Item 377)
    - Greenberg, Allen, undated (Item 192)
    - Greenberg, Benjamin, Nov 1981 (Item 1087)
    - Greenberg, Robert, undated (Item 646)
    - Greenberg, Samuel L., undated (Item 368)
    - Greene, Edward J., Sr., profile shot, Mar 1982 (Item 5541)
    - Greene, Jay, Dr., Board of Education, undated (Item 439)
    - Greenstein, Oscar, undated (Item 5050)
    - Greer, Alma, undated (Item 967)
    - Greyson, Doris, Vestal Regional Office, undated (Item 4242)
    - Grieco, Salvatore J. (Assemblyman), undated (Item 136)
    - Griffin, Francis J., undated (Item 3217)
    - Griffin, James, Sep 1974 (Item 3193)
    - Griffith, Ed, 1974 (Item 3282)
    - Griffiths, Daniel E., Dr., undated (Item 954)
    - Griggs, Allen, addresses Brooklyn student council, Mar 18, 1973 (Item 2241)
    - Grigorenko, Pyotr, Major General, Dec 1973 (Item 2842)
    - Grisi, Donna, Nov 1975 (Item 3938)
    - Grove, Vincent, NYSUT Manager, profile, Mar 1982 (Item 4981)
    - Grover, Malcolm P., undated (Item 586)
    - Gruber, Elias S., undated (Item 3779)
    - Gruber, Gene, Moravia TA, undated (Item 4953)
    - Grubiak, Rodney, with nurses at Bronx opening, Jan 1980 (Item 5361)
    - Gruen, Margery, Feb 4, 1973 (Item 2191)
    - Gruening, Ernest, undated (Item 282)
    - Grumet, Louis, State Ed Deptartment Assistant Comm. For Education of Handicapped Children, profile shot, Dec 1981 (Item 5353)
    - Guiffreda, Leon, undated (Item 3204)
    - Guigno, Matt, May 1976 (Item 4233)
    - Guinan, Matthew, undated (Item 295)
    - Guinan, Matthew, International President, Transport Workers Union of America, AFL-CIO, undated (Item 123)
    - Guir, Annette, undated (Item 878)
    - Gulotta, Thomas with Pat Koenig and Manny Kafka, undated (Item 5130)
    - Guthman, Raoul, Nov 1974 (Item 3391)
    - Gutter, Sheila, John Adams HS, Jun 1974 (Item 3144)
    - Haas, Eric, undated (Item 672)
    - Haberman, Lucille, undated (Item 950)
    - Haberman, Samuel receives George Meany Scouting Award, Feb 1976 (Item 4059)
    - Habgar, Kenneth, 1973 (Item 2606)
    - Hackett, Gary, undated (Item 4563)
    - Hagen, John, undated (Item 221)
    - Haley (Assemblyman), views on pending legislation, Apr 1976 (Item 4301)
    - Haley, Daniel K., undated (Item 3233)
    - Hall, Paul, undated (Item 325)
    - Hallett, George, undated (Item 911)
    - Halperin, Donald M. (Senator) delivering 20,000 letters on budget cuts from District 22 parents, students, teachers, etc., to Governor Rockefeller's office, May 1971 (Item 1531)
    - Halstead, Fred, undated (Item 824)
    - Halstead, Tom, undated (Item 4929)
    - Hamel, Alzor and Frank Murone review flyer to help pass tax limits referendum for Glenns Falls, Feb 1976 (Item 4136)
    - Hamilton, Charles T., Oct 1974 (Item 3344)
    - Hamilton, Ronald W., Jun 1974 (Item 3158)
    - Hamilton, Thelma, undated (Item 796)
    - Hanfield, Ray with P.R. Conklin at AFT Convention, undated (Item 4527)
    - Hanley, Arlene, SRP, undated (Item 5183)
    - Hanley, James M., undated (Item 1991)
    - Hanley, Mary Ellen (Solvay TA President), undated (Item 5169)
    - Hansen, Stephen C., undated (Item 873)
    - Hantman, Jessie, undated (Item 40)
    - Harding, Vincent, Professor, undated (Item 870)
    - Hardman, Elaine, undated (Item 4695)
    - Harms, Barbara [Includes but may not be limited to:] Duesberg, Gary, undated (Item 2498)
    - Harrington, Donald, Reverend, undated (Item 305)
    - Harrington, Michael, undated (Item 37)
    - Harris, Fred, Apr 1976 (Item 4172)
    - Harris, Fred (Senator, Oklahoma), undated (Item 505)
    - Harris, James with Al Shanker giving testimony on school violence, Jun 1975 (Item 3731)
    - Harris, Jim (NEA President, Elect), Jul 1974 (Item 918)
    - Harris, Joan, May 1973 (Item 2559)
    - Harris, Leonard D., undated (Item 602)
    - Harris, Sid, undated (Item 332)
    - Harris, Sid Memorial, May 1980 (Item 17)
    - Harris, Sid with Jeanette DiLorenzo, undated (Item 17)
    - Harris, Sid, Grove of Trees Dedication in Israel, Sep 1981 (Item 17)
    - Harris, Sid, JLC [Jewish Labor Committee] Educators Chapter, undated (Item 17)
    - Harrison, Hollis, Oct 1974 (Item 3322)
    - Harte, Thomas, undated (Item 3068)
    - Hartman, Arthur J., undated (Item 2494)
    - Hastings, James F., undated (Item 2106)
    - Hausbeck, Albert J., undated (Item 3226)
    - Hausrath, Gordon, Oct 1974 (Item 3376)
    - Havighurst, Robert J., undated (Item 863)
    - Hawkins, David addressing conference sponsored by the Workshop Center for Open Education at the City College of New York, Jun 1975 (Item 3699)
    - Hay, Louis, undated (Item 634)
    - Haynesworth, Clement F., undated (Item 955)
    - Heath, Bob, Apr 1974 (Item 2996)
    - Heath, Robert C., Mar 1974 (Item 2942)
    - Heath, Robert C., undated (Item 4094)
    - Hechinger, Fred, undated (Item 5603)
    - Hecht, Burton, Oct 1974 (Item 3385)
    - Hecht, Jay, UFT Spring Conference, 1981 (Item 5450)
    - Heiferman, Robert, North Rockland TA President, Jun 1975 (Item 3760)
    - Heitner, Henry, undated (Item 401)
    - Heitner, Lou, undated (Item 72)
    - Held, Harold, Jul 1975 (Item 3796)
    - Hellenbrand, Gail (Assemblywoman), undated (Item 91)
    - Helt, Dane, undated (Item 2493)
    - Henning, John F., undated (Item 4)
    - Henrieta, Elmer, Feb 1974 (Item 2883)
    - Hentoff, Nat, undated (Item 203)
    - Herder, Milton, undated (Item 217)
    - Herman, De Kalb CSTA, undated (Item 5265)
    - Herman, Roslyn, undated (Item 4944)
    - Hernandez, Ramon, Jan 1976 (Item 3983)
    - Hernandez, Ramon, Feb 1976 (Item 4060)
    - Herndon, Terry E., Apr 1973 (Item 2332)
    - Herrman, Richard, Valley Stream, undated (Item 5590)
    - Hertman, Walter, undated (Item 4894)
    - Hess, Terry and Marge Secrest, Oct 1975 (Item 4055)
    - Heumann, Judy, undated (Item 1254)
    - Hevesi, Alan (Assemblyman) speaking at PS 119 Bronx, Apr 1974 (Item 2997)
    - Hevesi, Alan G., undated (Item 1971)
    - Hichey, Jean, undated (Item 5037)
    - Hicks, Cheryl, undated (Item 5063)
    - Hicks, Doris (paraprofessional) [UFT?], undated (Item 5499)
    - Hicks, John, Reverend, Jun 1974 (Item 3105)
    - Hierholzer, Bob, Jun 1974 (Item 3159)
    - Higgins, George G. (Msgr.), reports on National Congress of Solidarity to [AFL-CIO] Food and Beverage Trades Department Convention, Nov 1981 (Item 5286)
    - Higgins, Robert, Nov 28, 1971 (Item 1726)
    - Hildebrant, Arthur, undated (Item 4717)
    - Hill, George, undated (Item 5766)
    - Hill, Herbert, undated (Item 428)
    - Hill, John, undated (Item 976)
    - Hill, Norman, Oct 1973 (Item 1707)
    - Hill, Velma, AFT Para [Paraprofessional] Conference, 1979 (Item 1079)
    - Hill, Velma, Award Certificate, Jun 17, 1971 (Item 1901)
    - Hill, Velma, concert in honor of Kallen with Glazer and Barb Tiller, Feb 1978 (Item 4839)
    - Hill, Velma, Paraprofessionals in Special Ed Manhattan Meeting, Jun 1979 (Item 1079)
    - Hill, Velma, speaking at Theodore Roosevelt HS, Mar 22, 1971 (Item 1573)
    - Hill, Velma, speaking at Theodore Roosevelt HS, Apr 1971 (Item 1691)
    - Hill, Velma, visiting PS 179 Queens, Jan 18, 1972 (Item 1715)
    - Hillman, Ponsie, Feb 3, 1980 (Item 462)
    - Hillman, Ponsie at JHS 271, Nov 1973 (Item 2746)
    - Hillman, Ponsie at NAACP Convention, Jul 1981 (Item 2746)
    - Hillman, Ponsie giving tour of UFT Headquarters, Nov 1973 (Item 2770)
    - Hillman, Ponsie with John Burnell, Velma Hill and Frank Brown, Mar 1975 (Item 3693)
    - Hillman, Ponsie with Julia Zozaya, meeting of National Advisory Committee, undated (Item 2802)
    - Hillson, Henry T., undated (Item 44)
    - Hinchey, Mauries D., Jr., undated (Item 4675)
    - Hirsch, Hyman, undated (Item 102)
    - Hirsch, Hyman, undated (Item 709)
    - Hirschen, William, RA 1985 (Item 5718)
    - Hirsh, Barbara with Bryna Levine, students in Intensive Language Program, Mar 1975 (Item 3725)
    - Hobart, Tom - Sweet, William; Benezra, Allen; Culinan, Martin, undated (Item 1781CR)
    - Hobart, Tom (President), reviews NEA War on State, May 1976 (Item 4375)
    - Hobart, Tom and Peter Peyser testify before Congress for emergency school aid bill, Jun 27, 1976 (Item 4496)
    - Hobart, Tom and Samuel Wakshull from United University Professions, May 1975 (Item 3848)
    - Hobart, Tom at Fordham University, May 1975 (Item 3756)
    - Hobart, Tom at Niagra Falls and Kenmore, Feb 1976 (Item 4343)
    - Hobart, Tom at NYU, Jun 1980 (Item 5001)
    - Hobart, Tom at Regents Legislative Conference 1976 (Item 4588)
    - Hobart, Tom at Union Label Convention receiving award and giving speech, Oct 1981 (Item 5001)
    - Hobart, Tom at Wellsville HS, Jan 1976 (Item 3982)
    - Hobart, Tom backs Newfane, NY teachers in fight to save teaching positions, May 1973 (Item 2567)
    - Hobart, Tom being interviewed by Marty Buskin from "Newsday", undated (Item 1844)
    - Hobart, Tom confers with Van Arsdale at AFL-CIO Convention, Nov 1981 (Item 1781)
    - Hobart, Tom leading discussion at breakfast meeting of NYS delegation at AFT Convention, undated (Item 4527)
    - Hobart, Tom outlines NYSUT position on CBTE, Jan 1975 (Item 3331)
    - Hobart, Tom speaking at Niagra Falls TA, Feb 1976 (Item 4096)
    - Hobart, Tom speaks out on Task Force Recommendations, Jun 27, 1976 (Item 4495)
    - Hobart, Tom visits Maple East School in Williamsville, NY, May 30, 1976 (Item 4389)
    - Hobart, Tom with Al Shanker, undated (Item 2461)
    - Hobart, Tom with Al Shanker at Batavia, Feb 1976 (Item 4002)
    - Hobart, Tom with Al Shanker, Dan Sanders, and Ed Rogers, undated (Item 2657)
    - Hobart, Tom with Antonia Cortese and George Meany, 1977 (Item 4864)
    - Hobart, Tom with Catherine Barrett, Jul 1973 (Item 1580)
    - Hobart, Tom with Dan Sanders, Jun 1973 (Item 2631)
    - Hobart, Tom with Dan Sanders receiving plaque at AFT Convention for "Outstanding Contributions", undated (Item 4534)
    - Hobart, Tom with Doris Knudsen, Feb 1974 (Item 2869)
    - Hobart, Tom with Ed Rogers, Jun 1973 (Item 2646)
    - Hobart, Tom with Ed Rogers and Vito DeLeonardis, Feb 1974 (Item 2874)
    - Hobart, Tom with Fran Moynihan and Ed Rogers at NYSUT Board Meeting, 1977 (Item 4864)
    - Hobart, Tom with Hiram Korpeck, Dec 1973 (Item 3448)
    - Hobart, Tom with Hugh Carey, Election Eve, undated (Item 5001)
    - Hobart, Tom with Irene McNulty and Catherine Barrett, May 1974 (Item 3083)
    - Hobart, Tom with John Farley, Nov 1974 (Item 3315)
    - Hobart, Tom with Ken Law, Sep 1974 (Item 3271)
    - Hobart, Tom with Mayor Erastus Corning of Albany, undated (Item 5001)
    - Hobart, Tom with Nick Maletta and Jim Gallahger, Dec 1974 (Item 1935)
    - Hobart, Tom with Olympics Artist Tom Geyer, undated (Item 5001)
    - Hobart, Tom with Toshikazu Momoyama, Nov 1974 (Item 3417)
    - Hobart, Tom, addressing Conference on Governing Education, undated (Item 2122)
    - Hobart, Tom, AFL-CIO Convention, undated (Item 4882)
    - Hobart, Tom, AFT COPE Awards Breakfast, on behalf of NYSUT, 1981 (Item 5001)
    - Hobart, Tom, Business Education Review Committee Hearing, Jun 1979 (Item 2461)
    - Hobart, Tom, NYSUT Board, 1979 (Item 4864)
    - Hobart, Tom, NYSUT Board, undated (Item 1791)
    - Hobart, Tom, NYSUT Board Meeting, 1977 (Item 4864)
    - Hobart, Tom, Panel on Property Taxes, Dec 1979 (Item 5001)
    - Hobart, Tom, Port Jefferson Station TA Representative Council, Feb 9, 1975 (Item 3546)
    - Hobart, Tom, signing of "Albany: Capital City on the Hudson," by John McEneny, gift to Albany High Schools by NYSUT, Feb 1982 (Item 1781)
    - Hoberman, L., undated (Item 998)
    - Hoberman, Lucille, undated (Item 1000)
    - Hochberg, Alan, Sep 1974 (Item 3185)
    - Hochberg, Samuel, undated (Item 667)
    - Hodgkinson, Harold L., undated (Item 3897)
    - Hoeckbruckner, LI Political Action, undated (Item 5592)
    - Hoffman, Helen (District 30 Election Candidate), Apr 1973 (Item 128)
    - Hoffman, S.L. and Mrs., undated (Item 922)
    - Hoffman, Samuel L., Feb 1976 (Item 4203)
    - Hogan, David, undated (Item 1983)
    - Hoggard, Georgina, undated (Item 961)
    - Holbert, Douglas instructing Reed Drum for the Special Olympics, May 1976 (Item 4371)
    - Holbrook, Charles E., Dec 1975 (Item 3965)
    - Holliday, Joy with Lou Ferretti, Oct 1974 (Item 3403)
    - Hollomon, Herbert, undated (Item 555)
    - Holmes, Betty, 1980 (Item 341)
    - Holmes, Betty, Testifying at Senate Education Committee Hearing, Feb 1981 (Item 5328)